Alexander O'Connor

alex.nderoconnor@gmail.com www.github.com/AlexOConnorHub www.linkedin.com/in/alexander-oc alexoconnor.us (317) 448-0475

Professional Summary

Highly motivated and skilled computer scientist focused on analytical problem solving with working knowledge in C, C#, C++, Java, Objective-C, PHP, Python, SQL, and the web stack. Over eight years of programming experience applying my passion to bring both personal and client visions to life via mobile, web, and server applications.

Experience

Computer Programmer - Center for Innovation and Research in Computing - Collegedale, TN

June 2021 - Present

- Design and implement features in software systems and applications
- Implement unit, functional, and acceptance tests
- Toolchains: C# WPF / ASP.net, Cocoa / Objective-C / Swift, C++, SWIG, Flutter / Dart, PHP, JavaScript, and JQuery
- Collaborate with team members to effectively divide tasks
- Leverage GitLab to track issues, new features, and team progress

A/V Tech - Southern Adventist University - Collegedale, TN

August 2019 - Present

- Designed custom application for implementing live vocal effects
- Manage live sound for events of up to 100 people
- Design stage lighting, customized for each event
- Manage equipment maintenance

IT Tech - Southern Adventist University - Collegedale, TN July 2019 - May 2021

- Created, designed, and deployed bootable tech USB images
- Provided technical support for Windows, Mac, and Linux
- Assisted clients though Jitbit service management

Education

Southern Adventist University - Collegedale Tennessee

July 2019 - December 2022

Bachelor of Science candidate, Computer Science (Cybersecurity)

Relevant Classes

Fundamentals of Programming and Software Design

Organization of Programming Languages

Data Structures & Algorithms

Database Management Systems

Operating Systems

Network Security

Advanced Network Security

Cyber Forensics